Eun Hyeon Park

07877322260, somnium.itineris@gmail.com
Portfolio - https://epark012.github.io/EunhyeonPark.github.io/

Summary

Story is the most powerful element in content creation, so that it has driven my journey to the present. From my education at Goldsmiths to the VR content development at UCL, I have chased the process of creating interactive environments that deliver cultures and its complexity. Based on experiences in the media industry and game development in Unity engine, I believe my education and my personal characteristics are suitable for this position.

Work Experience

UCL Multimedia Anthropology Lab, 08.2021 - Current

• As a VR developer, my task is to create a museum in virtual space.

Medici Development Centre, 11. 2020 - 06.2021

Develop virtual reality project based on the target devices (Oculus, Vive, Sym4d)

Somnium Studio, 07. 2019 - 10. 2020

Start-up, producing virtual reality contents making storytelling with customised stories.

Air force, 05. 2011 - 04. 2013

• Sergeant, discharged upon completing military service.

Education

- Goldsmiths, London 09.2015 09.2018
 - o BA, Media and communication
- University College London, London –09.2018
 - o MA, Ethnographic and Documentary Film (VR/AR)

Skills

- Game Engine Unity3D (Intermediate) & Unreal (Basic)
- Graphic Software Blender (Intermediate), Substance painter (Intermediate), Houdini (Basic), Photoshop (Basic)
- C# (Intermediate) & C++(Basic) & HLSL (Basic)
- Git